https://ruaf.org/privacy-policy/

Version of Jan 2020
RUAF processes personal data and other data in compliance with the applicable laws. We feel very strongly about privacy, and handle personal data with all due care.
You can contact RUAF at info@ruaf.org to access or modify your data whenever you wish. You can use the same email address to inform us if you no longer wish to receive updates about our work.
Read on to find out how RUAF handles personal data.
Scope of applicability
The present privacy policy applies to all processing operations concerning personal information (hereinafter: ‘Personal Data’) and data acquired from individuals’ visits to and use of RUAF’s website.
By visiting our website or subscribing to our newsletter, you accept this privacy policy and give your consent to RUAF to collect and store your data and process them in the manners described in the present policy.
Data processing
RUAF ensures that the systems in which Personal Data are stored have appropriate organisational and technical security. This serves to ensure that Personal Data are accessible only by employees whose jobs carry the necessary authorisation and that we use the Personal Data only for the purposes for which they were acquired and for compatible purposes. In so far as RUAF engages service providers to assist with recordkeeping or providing information, the use of the data and the security measures implemented by those parties are recorded in data processing agreements.
Your data will not be disclosed to other third parties without your explicit consent, except where it is required by law to disclose those data.
Data from newsletter subscribers are removed as soon as the individual unsubscribes.
Data collected through the Internet
RUAF collects Personal Data through its website. This happens when a visitor subscribes to our email newsletter.
Email
When RUAF sends out electronic mailings, we use a system that provides information about the method used for opening the email. That system also offers the possibility of tracking whether readers click on the links in our emails. RUAF does this to align the information provided to you more closely to your interests.
To withdraw your consent for receiving information by email, use the unsubscribe link in the appropriate email or else contact RUAF by sending an email to info@ruaf.org.
Cookies
RUAF uses cookies: tiny text files that Internet pages store on a visitor’s PC, tablet or mobile telephone. Those cookies are used to improve the user-friendliness of RUAF’s website and to monitor visits to those websites.
You can disable or delete cookies whenever you wish. You can adjust the settings in your browser to notify you as soon as you receive a cookie, or else to disable cookies. However, this might interfere with the website’s optimum performance.
Google Analytics
RUAF uses Google Analytics to collect information about details such as the date and time of your visit to our website and the pages that you viewed. RUAF uses these data for improving its website, compiling traffic statistics (e.g. the times of day or the days of the week when the website receives the highest numbers of visitors) and for assessing the popularity of the various parts of the website. RUAF only uses these data in aggregated form, and cannot trace them back to particular devices or individuals. You can install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to stop our website from forwarding information about your visits to Google Analytics.
Social networks
Our websites contain buttons and widgets for Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn social networks, to make it easier for you to share RUAF news with friends. Those social networks are connected to webservers that can trace your activity on our website and combine the results with other information from other websites. Social media cookies are only stored if you are logged in to the relevant media while visiting the RUAF website and if you give permission. You can disable this function by installing a program such as Disconnect for Chrome and Firefox.
Questions
If you have any questions about how RUAF processes your Personal Data, and what Personal Data RUAF processes, please contact RUAF at info@ruaf.org.
RUAF reserves the right to update its privacy policy. We recommend that you check this privacy policy regularly for any changes.
See also
publication
/
November 19, 2020
A food systems assessment of the Sustainable Diets for All programme in Uganda and...
Multi-actor initiatives in action: Lessons from the Sustainable Diets for All prog...
